George Koutanis

I am a full stack developer experienced in Javascript and React. I am originally from Greece and now live in Southampton, UK. While growing up my engagement with computers led me to appreciate the range of possibilities with technology and sparked my passion for programming.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

General

JavaScript

Backend

NodeJS ExpressJS REST MongoDB PostgreSQL

Frontend

React HTML CSS

Tools and technologies

Visual Studio Code
Mocha/Jest
Git+GitHub
Docker
AWS
TDD
Agile work methods

Links

LinkedIn GitHub

Languages

Greek - Native English - Proficient

EDUCATION & TRAINING

Full Stack Javascript - School of Applied Technology </salt>

January 2023 - April 2023 Intensive three month training program with a focus on TDD, mob programming, and applied learning.

IEK AGIOU DIMITRIOU

September 2017 - June 2019 Associate's degree Web Development-Design

WORK EXPERIENCE

Coopervision UK

September 2022 - december 2022

Royal Mail Southampton

December 2019 - August 2022 Mail center worker

Athens international airport Post office

March 2019 - September 2019 Mail center worker

Greek Customs office

September 2018 - February 2019 Customs agent assistant. Responsible for managing paperwork and assisting in IT related problems.

Hellas Electronics

August 2014 - December 2015
Office assistant responsible for handling emails - sales on ebay, editing images and listing products on ebay.